Hey everyone and thanks for jumping back
into the cryptoverse. Here we are with
another episode of NFA Live. We have Rob
from Digital Asset News. How's it going
Rob?
>> Good. Hello everybody.
>> Thanks for being here. And then we also
have Nick from Coin Guru. We haven't had
Nick on the channel in a while, so it's
a pleasure to to see you again.
>> Thanks for having me, Ben. Great to be
here with you guys.
>> Yeah. So, uh I would say pretty
interesting time in the market, but it's
not really. It's kind of boring.
[laughter]
Um, but we can at least talk about it.
Uh, so the first thing I I want to say
is with with Bitcoin, I mean, it hasn't
hasn't really done anything for a really
long time. We're just kind of hanging
out at 60K. I guess my question is, you
know, what are the odds here we get a
little bit of relief in the summer or do
you think that's unlikely? It's kind of
I mean, obviously, no one knows, right?
It's hard to time counter trend rallies,
but what do you guys think? Uh, Nick,
I'll start with you. What do you think
here about Bitcoin? Could it could it
find any relief in the short term or
what do you think?
>> Oh, we hope so, Ben. Eh, I mean, many of
the bottom signals have fired. E, we've
had like more than 50% of the onchain
Bitcoin supplies held at a loss. We've
had the monthly RSI at its lowest level
in 17 years or second lowest level.
We've had the M the Zed score at close
to 1.5 standard deviations in terms of
onchain valuations again. So there's a
lot of things that have fired in terms
of we've had a we close to a bottom or
had the bottom but and historically
summer is a mixed is mixed. You know
July can bounce, August is is quite
mixed, September gets ugly and then uh
October let's rather not talk about it.
Um what I'm looking forward and on the
on the charts in terms of things I want
to see a solid recovery of the 200E um
simple moving average and we're on the
cusp of that right now. I'd want to see
solid ETF inflows because we've had a
terrible outflow month last month. So,
I'd want to see at least three to three
to four days of solid inflows uh and
sustained inflows. And one of the best
indicators to watch as well in terms of
institutional accumulation is the
Coinbase premium. Quite a few people
quote that on X as well. This is
basically the differential between the
price of Bitcoin on Coinbase and in
offshore exchanges. gives an indication
of bullishness in uh in the US market
institutions.
Maybe if we could see some clarity from
strategy uh in terms of you know what
what's happening with there because
that's a big overhang on the markets. Um
but I think mainly it's also like ris
the macro is the biggest player right
now. Uh the risk on macro is that I mean
right now the risk on macro is that the
that we get some sort of a peace deal in
Iran and that breathes some life into
the markets. But if you guys have seen
the uh the you know what's happened
since the past few days, it seems as if
that's also off the cards right now with
the resumption of a few fights here in
the Middle East and that would lead to a
a strong dollar and then potentially um
you know the whole thing kicks off
again. Uh so it could go either way
depending on where the macro goes in the
next few in the next few weeks. Um, but
in my opinion, I think probably
rangebound between 62 uh 68K depending
on how the macro breaks either way.
>> Yeah, I mean it seems reasonable. I
don't A lot of times in the summer
markets are just kind of boring. I guess
everyone's on vacation going to the
World Cup, not trading Bitcoin. Rob,
what do you think? What What are you
seeing down in your neck of the woods?
>> No, Nick said it perfectly. I mean,
everything he just talked about is
essentially what's playing out. And uh
we can see that summer's kind of sucked.
There's a reason why they say sell in
May and go away. I think some people may
have actually wanted to do that. But the
I guess the bigger question is the
people watching the video is do you want
it to recover? And everybody talks about
how great it is to recover, but these
prices below 200E moving averages below
250 week. Why wouldn't you just keep it
there? I am uh quite happy with it being
just like the way it is.
Well, I mean, I tend to agree with you
guys. I mean, I who knows what happens
later in the year, but I I you know, we
talked about it similar to like some of
the prior midterm year bare markets.
It's interesting in 2022, there was a
nice little rally um for alts, but in
2018, alts got annihilated in July and
August. So, just remember like we're
talking about Bitcoin and not like all
the random junk that's that's out there.
Uh, next question. And and I think I
think Nick already touched on this a
little bit, so I'll just start with
Nick. Um, what do you think about
monetary policy? I mean, I I know that
we're looking at a potential rate hike
by the Fed. maybe you can fill us in on
on, you know, what's going on in your
neck of the woods, but is it are we
really going to get rate hikes with oil
coming down? I mean, oil's dropped a lot
and still seems like the Fed and and
some other um big players are still
looking at at tighter monetary policy.
Do you think that's actually going to
play out?
>> I think it could be. There's a few
factors here. one in terms of your point
around the oil that is true over the
past few weeks but I think that this
resumption in fighting could be another
catalyst which drives it higher and it
has we've had a spike in the past few
days um in in the previous um hormuse
crisis some of the reasons as to why oil
didn't spike much more than it did is
because of uh the SPR release in the US
and also uh China dropping its oil
imports by a considerable amount so that
helped abate some of the inflationary
pressures driven by oil. So, I don't
know if that's necessarily going to play
out if we do have another hormous
crisis. So, then you've got some cost
push inflation coming through. Um, but
we did have the the Fed minutes out
yesterday and they were quite hish. You
saw that half of the um Fed governors
wanted to were voting for an in rate
hike by the end of the year. And what's
also quite interesting, I don't know if
you saw this, Ben, but uh they said that
they they raised the the concern of
demand driven inflation from the AI
buildout specifically as it relates to,
you know, the chips and the memory and
how it's impacting on consumer goods. So
there you've got another uh cost push in
in the demand pull inflation from that.
Uh and then I think also Walsh himself
is generally being quite hawkish and it
doesn't help the fact that he hasn't
he's gone away with any sort of forward
guidance. So it makes it difficult for
us to assess. Um and indeed consumer
inflation expectations are still quite
high. I think we had the uh inflation
expectations from the New York Fed come
out last week which were the highest in
nearly three years.
>> And indeed the markets are moving in
that way as well. The 10 year now is
back. I think we had a 10-year auction
yesterday with the highest uh yield uh
since February of last year. So I think
that we still in in territory where the
Fed is going to be hish towards the end
of the year. Uh and if the oil crisis
does if we do have an additional whoo
crisis that could continue to push
inflation higher.
>> Yeah, I feel like the geopolitical stuff
is stuff I can't really nail down that
much. I I don't I feel like I just have
no idea like what to expect from from
Trump uh or I mean anything from that
matter from the geopolitical
perspective. It makes it really
difficult to try to guess what's going
to happen. But I guess there must be
something in there keeping you know rate
hikes on the table. So you're probably
right, Rob. I mean yeah, go ahead, Nick.
>> Yeah, I mean like the geopolitical angle
is a box of chocolates. You don't know
what you're going to get, right? You
never know. I mean, we thought that we
were going to we really thought that
we're moving towards like a risk-on
atmosphere with oil coming down and we
could continue the rally and the peace
deal would be signed and again it just
kicks off again. So, you never know.
>> Yeah, you never know what mood is going
to is going to happen. Um Rob, I know
monetary policy isn't necessarily your
favorite topic.
It's not it's not like we're talking
about chess or something, but if you
could chime in
>> kind of fill in I mean I'll just echo
what I mean just to just to give
everybody a a a visual about what's
actually happening. If you want to throw
this up, this is just to touch on what
oil is. You know, we're going to hear
this again and again. Trump's going to
say everybody's a liar and he's the only
one that's right. And that's fine. And
there's going to be a memorandum of
understanding that's going to get passed
through and people are going to go
through and just say, "No, no, we're not
going to do this this pre peace deal."
It's going to just be
erratic. And that's pretty much what it
is. And I know people would say, "Well,
it's the oil price." And they they take
a look at it and, you know, like today,
okay, it is what it is. It's up, you
know, plus 0.49, but if you take a look
at like a month
and then one year,
I mean, yeah, this is where you see that
inflation talk coming in. Now it's going
down. So you would think that okay well
inflation is going to be just just e
ebbed away because at some point the oil
will go down. The problem is and Nick
touched on it is AI and the big problem
is is that there are different sectors
in the world especially here in the
United States as they start to build
these data centers the price of
electricity goes up. So you have on one
side inflation you know going down with
with the price of oil going down.
Another side you have electricity going
up for your for your home
you know usage and business usage. So in
that case you got one going up one going
down there might be an issue there. And
AI I think is the big play right now. If
you take a look at stocks and things
that are going up it's looking pretty
good. But um you know I don't know where
things are going as far as like uh
inflation. I think the Fed is going to,
like Nick said, it's going to be very
hawkish and I think there's going to be
some I mean potentially some rate hikes.
So, we'll see.
>> Did you guys see the news that um the
Fed is now going about changing uh how
they measure PCE, slight tweaks in the
in the measurement of PCE and that Walsh
is also targeting some other version of
PCE called the trimmed PCE. basically
trying to kind of slightly move the
goalpost. So, you know, they they can't
get the actual headline CPE, PCE number
under 2%. So, they kind of like
>> if you don't count inflation correctly,
it's not really a problem, right?
>> That's right. It's all how you get this
move the data.
>> Yeah. I thought about that like when you
like publish papers and stuff like I I
just can't imagine like changing the
methodology of of how you calculate a
data series halfway through or part of
the way through and then like putting it
on the same chart and and expecting
people to to take anything away from it.
It's like it's literally just calculated
differently. So, who knows? But now that
we got the boring stuff, some of the
boring stuff out of the way, let's get
to the exciting stuff, the World Cup.
So, um, I'm obviously wearing an
Argentina jersey. It's because I I just
went to the game. I think I'm honestly
it was probably one of the best games
I've ever been to. I think it was the
best game I've ever been to. That was
exciting. I mean, I It was the 78th
minute or 79th minute, I believe, and
Argentina was down two zero
>> and and they got three goals in like 15
minutes and ended up winning. Um,
>> so I ended up I mean, I got the jersey
and and whatnot. What do you guys think
for the World Cup? Nick, are you looking
at uh England? Is it Is it finally
coming home? [laughter]
>> I don't know, man. Unfortunately, I
can't say. So, I know they got up with
Norway and I I kind of predict that um
you know, in true England style, they're
going to go out on penalties,
unfortunately. [laughter]
>> Yeah,
>> I know. I don't tell guy I said that,
but uh you know, they haven't been one
of the stronger teams, unfortunately,
although they they managed to get
through. Uh I think that France seems
like they the best all round team. You
know, they've won every match. They've
they comfortably beat Sweden. Um they
look balanced in attack and defense. Uh
Spain has got strong defense. Uh you
know, so if they manage to get us a goal
in any of the games, they can hold it
out. But um you know, there's going to
there could be some upsets here. There
could be some real big upsets. So I
don't know. Hey,
>> what do you think Holland? Because I
mean he's been fun to watch. And you
know, didn't wasn't it uh wasn't it Kane
that missed the penalty against France
in 2022 that was the equalizer? Am or am
I not remembering that right?
>> I I can't recall, but yeah, England's
got a very bad reputation when it comes
to penalty shootouts in World Cups. Like
it's the bane of their existence,
so I don't know. Um but yeah, I mean I
think that France has got the um the
edge here. Argentina, I like I think
that you know, you were just talking
about the the game there. It was quite
fascinating to watch. Actually, I was
watching the exact moment on Poly Market
on on on Kelshi how the odds were
changing and it was it's more exciting
than tracking the chart of an altcoin to
be honest.
>> Yeah,
>> it's pretty crazy.
>> Uh but yeah, Argentina Messi is strong.
He's but you can't just rely on one
player. I think that they came close in
a few of the games.
>> Uh I I just looked it up. It was 2022.
So England was ahead of France two or
sorry England was behind France 2 to1
and then they received a penalty in like
the 84th minute. Harry Kane took the
penalty and he and he sent it high. He
sent it above the goal. So they missed
the equalizer and then they lost the
game. So it was a heartbreak. It was a
heartbreak and you could kind of I mean
what they didn't really go out on
penalties but it was a penalty that
would have allowed them to to tie
>> and and
>> yeah it's going to be a tough game I
think against Norway because they got to
go up against uh Holland and he's got a
lot of he's
>> he's got a lot of
>> Viking.
>> Yeah. Rob, who do you got? Who do you
got winning? I mean a lot of a lot of
the I mean the US is out, Canada's out,
Mexico's out. Um who do you got? I have
no idea. I I'll I I'll just say this. I
I took Ben's advice because, you know, I
heard about how great the World Cup was.
So, I went and watched uh America verse
Belgium and it was the worst game I've
ever seen in my life as they lost 4-1.
I'm like, "Well, this was trash." So,
thank you, Ben, for dashing my hopes and
dreams as I watch America get crushed.
>> Why should today be any different than
any other day, Rob?
>> Exactly. Oh,
>> no. I mean, like that was a bad game and
I I mean I wanted I wanted the US to win
the whole thing, but I mean practically
speaking, that's just not going to
happen, you know.
>> I want to ask Americans though, what did
you guys think of the the red card
itself? Forget about the political, you
know, the political angle. I mean, the
actual red card that was given to him.
>> I have mixed feelings about it. Like I
mean, I I think from the still image
alone, it looks like a red card, right?
Like from the still image alone, if you
look at the whole context, I mean, it
does look like it does look like he was
in front of the ball and then the other
player kind of like ran up and and kind
of made him stumble.
>> So, I don't know. I mean, I do think
though, yeah, I thought about this a
lot. I I don't think that two wrongs
make a right. So, even if it even if I
don't think it should have been a red
card, once it was a red card,
>> I don't think I don't agree with them
suspending it and and allowing him to
play. I mean, I just I don't know. Like
I I just don't think that because it
kind of sets the wrong precedent in some
ways because then a lot of other teams
could could make the same claim. Like
they could be like, "Well, take this
yellow card away or take that red card
away." And I I think that regardless of
what anyone says, I mean, look, the
president of the United States called
FIFA and then a decision was made that
has never been made in the World Cup
before. I mean, I know that I know that
Cristiano Ronaldo had some uh had some
stuff suspended as well so he could play
in the World Cup, but I don't know. I
think it just looks bad. Like, it looks
bad. And the US had so much momentum,
>> like just like good m I'm not saying
they were going to win, you know,
against Belgium regardless. I'm just
saying they had like
>> good momentum, I think, in terms of like
the narrative surrounding them. And I
just kind of feel like that tainted
>> um the narrative for a lot of a lot of
people. Well, I I I would say this, if I
were if I were anywhere else in the in
the world besides the United States, I
would be absolutely fuming that that red
card was was uh suspended. Even though I
don't know that I agree that it should I
don't know that it should have been
read. I
>> I think it was Yeah, definitely one of
the worst FIFA calls, only surpassed by
the um even more so than the uh FIFA
Peace Prize.
>> Wait, what do you think was the worst
call? The red card or taking it away or
>> uh No, definitely taking it away. the
red card I think you can debate it but
taking it away uh I think yes there and
I think it's just like because and UEFA
put it best it's like you know it goes
to the integrity of the game and like
other teams can also come out and
complain about that right if you don't
have some clear guidance in terms of how
and and a protocol and process for this
right not just an executive decision by
um the FIFA president
>> right yeah and I I just don't feel like
there was a ton of transparency you know
about it and I think that just makes it
worse for for other teams because it
does feels kind of weird. Um, and I it's
weird like rooting for the team that it
happened to, but also like empathizing
with everyone else being like, "Yeah,
like you guys have a point." Um, but
look, Belgium played really well and the
US didn't. I mean, they just they had an
awful game. Um, Belgium deserves to go
on, right? I mean, that's just and and
look, the the US is no stranger to
losing uh in the round of 16, you know?
like this is a very a very common
occurrence. So I mean who do we have
left? We have I mean Morocco and France
play today, right?
>> Yeah, that's going to be a crazy one.
>> Uh you know they that's because they
played in the 2022 game as well in the
2022 World Cup and it was two-0 I
believe to France. Morocco advanced I
think it was the first semi-final
something when an African team in the
first semi-final but yeah there's a lot
writing on that as well. You know,
>> this guy's a comment. I just want to
address that. Messi had the same play in
the group stage and getting to yell. I
agree. Like there's the same still image
for Messi, but this is one of those
things where like we can't we can't
always point to something that didn't
get called and say that nothing else
ever gets called just because one foul
wasn't called. Yeah. You know, and I
think that's the hard part because it's
like the natural reaction. And I had
that reaction too. I'm like and I like
Messi. I mean, like I mean, I just got
to see him play, but just because one
foul isn't called doesn't mean that
other fouls I think it should have been
at least a yellow. Like I think a yellow
definitely makes sense. I'm just not
sure about a red. Um, but all right. Uh,
this guy says, "Oops, wrong sweep."
[laughter]
I mean, how else are you going to get
through the midterm year? I mean, the
World Cup is is how you get through it.
All right. Uh, let's get to back to the
boring questions. Um, Rob, you have a
Clarity Act update.
Yeah, it's probably not going to pass.
Uh, what else you want to know
>> ever or this year?
>> No, just this year. I mean, I don't
think it's going to happen right now
because there's a because as a reminder
everybody that we have to get a super
majority of 6040 means a lot of
Democrats have to come over and that's
not going to happen. They want a
provision which essentially gets out uh
officials and their family members of
trading uh digital assets in
cryptocurrency. And as we just saw with
Donald Trump, he made a couple of almost
$1.4 4 billion off of that. So, I don't
know if that's actually going to go
through. So, I mean, good luck. I mean,
if it does, it'll be a nice catalyst and
that would change everything, but I just
don't see it actually happening. Sorry.
>> No, I mean, I I mean, you got to say it
like it is. Nick, do you have uh any any
different view on that or you agree with
>> I don't think that's very very well put.
I think that um unfortunately, that's
the main sticking point. That's what
it's going to be. Uh I think that they
want they want some sort of ethics
provision provisions in there and um it
you know may have had bit more chance a
few months ago but after that that
disclosure of the uh of the profits made
by Trump and his and his family from
these from crypto ventures it's
politically toxic to support this as a
Democrat um if you if you don't have any
sort of provisions that bar this and the
only other question is would Trump and
Kobe be willing to have those provisions
in there and not be able to trade crypto
and not be able to invest in crypto
projects for the greater good of the
crypto community to get this bill
passed. I don't know. Is he a benevolent
uh leader in that sense? We'll have to
see, but I don't think so. I think it's
unlikely. Um and probably not. Yeah, if
it's not happening this year, what if
Dems win the house? That's not
happening.
>> Yeah, seems fair. What do you guys think
about Sailor? I mean, that's the I think
that's the biggest elephant in the room
these days in crypto is sailor selling.
And, you know, I think there's a lot of
people don't want to really talk about
it, but I mean, look, it's happening.
It's it's it's certainly a strong
narrative. Um, what do you guys think
about it? I mean, is he is it seems like
the public opinion is is somewhat
changing and and some people are upset
because they're like, "What happened?
Never sell." I I mean, I'm not going to
criticize Sailor. I mean, if I if I'm
willing to sell Bitcoin occasionally,
why would I say someone else can't, you
know? I mean, what do you guys think,
though? Any I mean, either you can take
it if you want,
>> Nick.
>> Oh, okay. I mean, so it's definitely
cleared some FUD to the extent that he's
trying to do something. Uh, he was in a
bit of a bind recently with of one MNAV
for MST for the strategy was below one,
which means any sort of issuance of uh
common stock would be diluted. So that
was a big problem. You the negative fly
flywheel effect. Um stretch was trading
considerably below par near um near near
default um technically default levels.
So it was really killing the market and
at least coming out with a plan. This
Bitcoin monetization plan was something.
Uh and look, sell pressure is never
good. And it's not the fact that that
he's only not buying, but there's the
potential sell pressure. We saw the 200
something million that was sold on
Monday. Uh but surprisingly Bitcoin kind
of rallied out of that because it's a
sense that they know in the monetization
plan I think it was up to 1.25 billion
that could be sold Bitcoin to buyback
stretch and MSTR. Uh so that at least
the market knows what the number is. Uh
I think that he should just and this is
what Gayscale has said as well just rip
the band-aid off and sell and sell a
stack of Bitcoin be a billy to get the
cash you need to last through the bare
market. Uh so I think that that could uh
could alleviate some of the concerns. Uh
but yeah, the optics optics are terrible
definitely from the the saint sailor of
Bitcoin accumulating and then and then
now saying and not necessarily for
people in the crypto space, but I think
if you look at a lot of the trady media,
the fact that you know he was saying
that you never sell your Bitcoin and now
he is and I think the data trade is just
completely dead and we've got this
overhang. So, I think it's still looking
dicey. Um, we have to see what happens
once he sold that. And one more point
I'll add there as well is um in terms of
the optics as well, I've heard on a few
podcasts in terms of institutional
players are less likely to want to buy
because of the massive overhang. They
say, "Okay, I'll just wait to see what
happens with strategy." But when you've
got such a big potential seller in the
market before I start buying. So, yeah,
that's it's not it's not looking too
good right now.
>> Yeah. Didn't he he there were a couple
of cells, right? Wasn't there a smaller
one like a few weeks ago and then just
another a larger one? You Rob, you think
he's building up to a big one?
>> I mean, that was that was quite a bit,
but I mean like like Nick was talking
about, uh they still do own like 830,000
plus Bitcoin. So, even though they sold
I think it was 3,000 over the last two
weeks or so, that's still not too much.
But I but I will say that I mean, as far
as like is it getting ready to to sell
even more? There was a there was a a
graphic that was put up and it talked
about the uh annualized rate of return
for for Bitcoin and Stretch. They said
that for what they just sold or what
they have right now, they can do a break
even to cover everything for essentially
over 31 years. And if it goes up by and
that's at if Bitcoin has no rate of
return of 0% for 31 years. If it goes up
just 3.3% it's essentially goes out to
infinity. So like with these these
things that are going on I I I don't
think it's as big as a deal as people
make it out to be. But the big thing was
and Ben you
what you said was I can't fault Sailor
for selling Bitcoin because I sell
Bitcoin. The difference is is that you
never on your channel or on Coin
Bureau's channel or my channel have ever
said you never sell your Bitcoin. You
hold on forever and then you know weeks
later, months later, years later say,
"Okay, so sorry. Rules for the
rules for me, not May I add, Robert,
it's not only that is that you should um
you should try and take out debt,
mortgage your house, and potentially
sell your kidney if you want to buy more
Bitcoin."
>> Exactly. You know, you know, when he
said that, that was that was when he he
came on my channel for the first time is
he he put out a tweet saying that you
should like take out a mortgage, a
second mortgage to to buy Bitcoin. This
is back in 2021.
>> And I said that was a really dumb idea.
And then he said he wanted to come talk
about it on my stream and then we talked
about it and I still don't agree. I
mean, I I think too like institutions
and retail are very different, right?
So, like if a if if a like if a retail
trader took out a second mortgage and
then Bitcoin crashed, which it did back
then in 2022, like that could have wiped
them out, right? They might not have had
the capital to survive all that and then
and then wait for the next bull market.
Whereas institutions can often survive
it because they have the capital to sort
of wait it out, which a lot of smaller
players don't necessarily have. I don't
know. So, I mean, I I mean, I' I'd be
lying if I I mean, I don't think it's
the best optics for Bitcoin that like
the biggest buyer has become a seller.
Um,
>> I don't I mean,
>> it's crazy that in terms of the polarity
as, you know, the contrast between him
selling some, but then I've Tom Lee is
still out there buying Ethereum.
[laughter]
>> That's right.
>> Yeah.
>> Still buying ETH. I'm like, what?
>> I got to tell you, I mean, some of like
the worst price predictions of all time,
but I'll hand it to Tom. he keeps buying
Bitcoin and he's going to go through and
he'll he'll probably do great because
he's buying in the bare market which is
what everybody's supposed to do. Not
financial advice, but that's usually
when when people make make the most most
money. I think Tom's going to come out
ahead. I feel like Sailor if he just
kept with the strategy of just buying
Bitcoin, but I feel then he launched
like all these different like financial
products and they're all like
intertwined and like I just feel like
he's he's overco complicated it so much
and and now I mean look I've said it for
for years that strategy over a long
enough period of time will likely
underperform Bitcoin. And maybe the
reason they underperform Bitcoin is
because they're forced to sell Bitcoin
to to uh make sure they can pay
shareholders. I don't know. One last
question because I saw it in the chat.
Nick, I want your answer on this one.
Okay. I know Rob, you don't care because
I I I feel very strongly about this.
>> What's your thoughts on the Croatia
offsides call? Did you watch that game?
>> I did not watch that game,
unfortunately. So, what happened was um
uh Croatia at at the very end the the
guy passed the ball into the box and it
like swiped by someone's hair on on
Croatia's team. Then Croatia got a goal
from that from a guy that would have
been off sides um from that point. So,
they scored. Now, when you watch it, you
cannot tell that the ball is um like you
can't tell that the ball is changes
direction, but they use V to overturn
it. I thought it was egregious. Uh but
we got to get going anyways.
>> I I believe Yeah, I did catch the
replays of that and that was crazy. That
was crazy. I mean, I feel so bad for
Croatia because also the one of the star
players, it was probably his last game
as well potentially in the World Cup.
>> Yeah.
>> All right, guys. I gotta run. It was
great to have you here. If you guys
aren't subscribed to Rob or Nick, make
sure you guys subscribe. Um, and I will
see you guys. We'll see you guys next
week on Rob's channel. Cheers, guys.
Adios.
>> Thanks for having me, Ben. Cheers.